Guide to the Margaret Wylie papers, 1926-1963.
Wylie, Margaret papers, 1926-1963.
- Series I. Cornell Study Clubs
  - Tompkins County
    - Mrs. Marguerite Dixon,Home Demonstration Agent, Court House, Ithaca, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Home Bureau Reports, etc., 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Tompkins County, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Brooktondale Child Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Clayton Weber (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Danby Child Study Club, Mrs. Leslie Birtch, R.D. 4, Ithaca, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Family Life Discussion, Mrs. Beatrice Reddick, Mitchell St., Ithaca (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Newcomers' Child Study Club, Mrs. Reynold Metz, 116 Ferris Place, Ithaca, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Ulster County
    - Ulster County - Kingston, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Kingston, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Miss Evelyn Nance, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Edgar M. Clarke, county leader, 1931-1940 (Box 11, Folder 50-52)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1932-1940 (Box 11, Folder 53-55)
    - Mrs. Rockwood's material, 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Mr. Endorfs material, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Mrs. Millard Davis, county leader, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Mrs. Raymond DuBois, New Paltz, NY study club, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. S. B. Taber, Milton, NY study club, 1931-1933 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. Milliard Davis, Kerhonkson, NY, 1931-1940 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. Edgar J Clarke, Milton, NY county leader, 1932-1938 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Kingston, NY study club, 1933-1939 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. F. H. Bond, Milton, NY Study Club and county leader, 1933-1939 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Mrs. Marie Braun, Kerhonkson, NY, 1933-1940 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Mrs. Harry Voss, Walkill, NY study club, 1934-1939 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. Jane La Valle, Napanoch, NY study club, 1934-1939 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Mrs. R. B. Webster, Allaben, NY study club, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Mrs. R. B. Webster, Shandaken, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Dr. N. Weintraub, Kingston, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Mrs. E. Sagendorf, Lake Katrine, NY, 1936-1940 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Marlboro, NY study club, 1936-1940 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. Clyde Hutton, Kingston, NY study club, 1936-1940 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Miss E. Wooley, Marlboro, NY Secretary., 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Mrs. Glenn Clarke, Milton, NY kindergarten mothers, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Mrs. Gertrude Bevier, New Paltz, NY, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Mrs. F. Black, Modena, NY, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Mrs. Frances Sherman, Kerhonkson, NY, 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Mrs. Archie Hall Davis, Kerhankson, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Mrs. Stephen Nagy, Kingston, NY study club, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Mrs. Edgar Freese, Kingston, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Everice Parsons, Home Demonstration Agent, 280 Wall St., Kingston, 1943-1945 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Ulster County, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - County Leader, Mrs. A.G.F. Van Laer, High Falls, NY, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Accord Home Study Club, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Ellenville-Kerhonkson-Accord Study Club, Mrs. Millard Davis, Kerhonkson, NY (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Rondout Family Life Group, Chairman Mrs. Ariella Sarine, Ellensville, NY; Mrs. Rose S. Joyce, Secretary, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Kingston Club III, Chairman S. Ryder; Eva R. Brink, Secretary, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Kingston Club II, Chairman Mrs. Leonard O'Reilly, Kingston, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Kingston Child Study Club II, Mrs. Kenneth Martin, Madison Ave., Kingston, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Kingston III, Mrs. Theresa Appenzeller, 59 N. Front St., Kingston, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Kingston IV Study Club, Chairman Mrs. John Morton, 56 Roosevelt Ave., Kingston, 1943-1945 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Kingston Club I, Chairman Mrs. A.L. Berwin, 27 Furnace St., 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Lake Katrine Study Club, Mrs. G. Parish, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Milton Study Club, Chairman M. Etta Wolley, Milton-Marlboro; Margaret Fourie, Secretary, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Mrs. Lester Arnold, Modena, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Modena Home Bureau Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Eldred Smith, Modena, NY, 1941-1945 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Mawak Child Study Club, Mrs. Sherman Loucks, 182 Canal St., Ellenville, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Forest Glen Study Club, Mrs. Floyd Funderson, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Mrs. Josephine Smith, New Salem, NY, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Saugerties Study Club, Chairman June Curtis, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Shawangunk Study Club, Phyllis Renson, 1942-1945 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Wallkill Study Club, Chairman Mrs. A.R. Bedell, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Worcester Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Franklin Kelder, Accord, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Warren County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1934-1940 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. Ethel Furlong, Rockwood, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. Beatrice Cameron, Athol, NY study club, 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Paul Boyce, Glens Falls, NY study club, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Belle Gleeson, Glens Falls, NY study club, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. A. Meade, Brant Lake, NY Horicon Group, 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. Paul Boyce, county leader, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Untitled, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. A. B. Prescott, North Creek, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Mrs. K. J. Clough, Lake George, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Mrs. C. R. Larose, Glens Falls, NY study club, 1936-1939 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Mrs. Joseph Hughes, Hadley, NY study club, 1936-1940 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Mrs. Culver, Pottersville, NY study group, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Mrs. Jay Morehouse, Johnsburg, NY study club, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Mrs. E. R. Carlisle, Glens Falls, NY, 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Mrs. Lincoln Tucker, Warrensburg, NY, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Mrs. Frank Wolfe, Glens Falls, NY study club, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Mr. Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Mrs. D. Gardner, Queensbury, NY study club, 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Mrs. Charles Noble, P.T.A. study club, chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Mrs. R. M. Bullock, study club, chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Mrs. D. H. Cornell, Glens Falls, NY study group, chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Mrs. Adam Sitterley, North Creek, NY study club, chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Talma Buster, Home Demonstration Agent, Warrensburg, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Adirondack Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Harold Bump, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Victory Study Club, Mrs. A.W. Parkhurst, Ft. Edward, NY, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Com. H.B. Study Club, Mrs. Raymond Bullock, R.D. #1, Glens Falls, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Glens Falls Study Club, Mrs. Margaret Reisig, Glens Falls, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Senior Broadacres Family Life Study Club, Chairman Mrs. H.H. Strong, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. Robert Buddy, Glens Falls, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. Walter Ingalls, 75 Crandall St., Glens Falls, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. J.F. Dundon, Glens Falls, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. E. Wellington, glen, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. G.W. Bartlett, glen, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Central Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Thomas Hogan, 4 Knight St., Glens Falls, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Mrs. Ben Kuby, Sherman Ave., Glens Falls, 1940-1944 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. Claud Remillard, Glens Falls Victory Unit, Glens Falls, 1940-1944 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Ideal Mothers Club, Mrs. L. Jones, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Lake George Study Club, Mrs. Bernard Ramsey, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Lake Luzerne Study Club, Mrs. Easterbrook, 1942-1945 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Knox Bishop, Luzerne, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - North Creek Study Club, Chairman Mrs. A. Sitterly, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - South Glens Falls Study Club, Mrs. Clayton F. Stewart, 27 Haveland Rd., S. Glens Falls, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Mrs. H. Savage, 7 Library St., Warrensburg, NY (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Mrs. Kenneth Joslyn, West Mountain, Glens Falls, 1942-1943 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Mrs. Paul Boyce, County Leader, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Washington County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - 4-H club, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Mrs. Clarence Slack, Study Club chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Mrs. W. Chapin, Tri-town Study Club chairman, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. Paul Boyce, county leader, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Untitled, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Mrs. Herbert Obenauer, East Green Bridge, NY study club, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Miss Vilma Golde, Home Demonstration Agent, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Home Bureau Reports, etc., 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Tri-Town Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Walter Chapen, Cambridge, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Monday Night Family Life Study Club, Mrs. Van Tasker, Fort Edward, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Mrs. E.V. Wiley, Hudson Falls, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Mrs. H. Obenauer, Middle Falls, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Cossayuna Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Nelson Pratt, Salem, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Wayne County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, Sodus, NY, 1930-1940 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. La Vern Pontius, Wolcott, NY study club, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. Ralph Miner, Wolcott, NY study club, 1931-1934 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Mrs. Clarence Huckle, Clyde, NY study club, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Mrs. Wayne Kelsey, Clyde, NY study club, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Miss E. Belle Conklin, Macedon, NY studyclub, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Mrs. Margeret Bowe, Palmyra, NY study club, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Mrs. M. E. Buckman, Sodus, NY countyleader, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Mrs. Rockwood, 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Mrs. Frank Henning, Walworth, NY study club, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Mrs. F. K. Mosher, Parents Study Club chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Mrs. Frank Henning, Walworth, NY Study Club chairman, 1938-193 9 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Mrs. Roy Lash, Clyde, NY Study Club chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Mrs. Irving Beal, Preschool Parent Education Study Club chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Mrs. Arthur Smith, Sodus, NY, School-Age Study Club of P.T.A. chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Mrs. A. L. Benedict, Parent Education Study Club chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Mrs. Paul Boyce, county leader, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Mrs. Fred Keller, chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Miss Ruth Caplan, Home Demonstration Agent, 2 Main St., Sodus, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - North Rose Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Gray Skutt, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - Westchester County
    - Westchester County (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - Wyoming County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, Wyoming County, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Mrs. Clara P. Richards, Perry, NY, 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Mr. Lemo Rockwood, Wyoming County, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Dr. Anne Viele, Dale, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Mrs. E.V. Gouinlock, Warsaw, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Mrs. K. Van Valkenburg, Warsaw, NY, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Wyoming County, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Reports of meetings in Home Bureau units, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Wyoming County, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Amelia D. Bielaski, Home Demonstration Agent, Warsaw, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Wyoming County, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Brick School Child Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Grace Koblas, R.D. #2, Attica, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 69)
  - Yates County
    - Yates County, 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - PennYan,NY, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Mrs. Ursula Daniels, Perm Yan, 1931-1933 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Mrs. Fred Martin, Branchport, NY, 1931-1933 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Miss Edith Nash, Home Demonstration Agent, 1931-1933 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Yates County, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Series II. Subject Files, Correspondence,Booklets, and Questionnaires
  - "Child Guidance for the Lay Leader." Marguerite Wilker. With lesson plans and completed lay leader reports. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Second-Year Child Study Program: Outline, references, evaluative surveys. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Student course evaluations of SI01 content, summer session 1934. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Raw data/materials (scenarios) for Flemmie Kittrel's thesis study. (5 parts) (Box 8, Folder 4-8)
  - Meeting and alliance charts, County and City Leader Week; Study Club annual reports and attendance, 1929-1934. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Student work: completed discussion tests on emotional behavior. (3 parts) (Box 8, Folder 10-12)
  - Goals Achieved in Child Development, Fall 1932-Spring 1933 (surveys): all clubs. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Summary of Achievements; Club Members' Record Books, 1937: Clubs grouped by county. (2 parts) (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
  - Summary of Achievements; Club Members' Record Books, 1938: Clubs grouped by county. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Student course evaluations, S1905 content: 1936. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Summary of Achievements; Club Members' Record Books: 1935-36. (3 parts) (Box 8, Folder 18-20)
  - Student work: discussion tests, child observation records. (4 parts) (Box 8, Folder 21-24)
  - Incident analysis surveys (worksheets), Jefferson County Conference Series: February-March, 1934 - Emotions; Parent-Child Cooperation; Child Guidance. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Questionnaires on eating and sleeping behavior, completed by Truxton group (Cortland County): 1935-36. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Margaret Wylie's work - mimeographed material 1926-27 (Box 9)
  - Brown paper parcel - eight year old report data; originals of last letter of child guidance series sent out in 1933; annual report by Dr. Wylie; Dr. Rockwood; Dr. Entorf (Box 9)
  - Incidents taken from Home Study Club Reports - 1931 -36 (Box 9)
  - Report of Club and Leader Groups - Sept. 1935-Mar. 15, 1936 (Box 9)
  - Study Club Report - 1928-29 (Box 9)
  - Annual Extension Report - Dec. 1933-Nov. 30, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Extension Report - Dec. 1934-Dec. 1935 (Box 9)
  - Cardboard file box - containing filing cards with notes (Box 9)
  - 1927-1928
    - Extension Conference Programs, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Farmers Week Programs, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - City Programs - Rochester, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Child welfare News Summary, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Club Leaders - Addresses, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Nursury School publicity - Katharine Reeves, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - County Organization Plan for Elem. Program - suggestions, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Health News, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - County Programs, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Extension Narrative, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Bibliographies, Books, Pamphlets - Child Guidance, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Bibliographies for Classes, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Bibliographies for Children, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Addresses - Parent Interviews Testing Children, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Memorandum - Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Merrill-Palmer, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Dean Mann -Ladd - Betten, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Waring-Fowler, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Requests - to be answered, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Agents Conference - Outlines; First and Second Year Programs, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Extension Committee - H. EC., 1927-1931 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 1928-1929
    - Present Statute of Child Guidance as a Home Economic Project, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 22a)
    - Cornell Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Study Clubs 1920, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Chautauqua County Clubs, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Committee on Family Life, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - 1929-1930
    - Request for Work in 1930-31, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Parent Teacher Association, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Stocking, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Club Form Letters, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Circular Letters from the College, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Information about Exhibits, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Photographs - Troy, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Conference Form Letters, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Erie County, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Cortland County - Cortland, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Brief Outline of Work, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Nassau County - Mineola, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Niagara County - Lockport, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Onieda County - Utica, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Onondaga County - Syracuse, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Rensselaer County - Troy, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Saratoga County - Saratoga Springs, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Steuben County, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - St. Lawrence County - Canton, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Wanye County - Sodus, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Lay Leader Correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - National Committee on Nursery Schools, 1929-3 0 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Conference Organization, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Andrus, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Kruse, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Dean Mann - Dr. Ladd, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Reports of Child Guidance, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Broome County - Binghamton, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Yates County - Penn Van, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Monthly Report - Eastman, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - White House Conference Material, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Magazines, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Spring Ext. Conference at the College, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Extension Conferences, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Extension Service News, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Trip Report - Wilker, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Trip Report - Eastman, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Questionnaire Summaries, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - 1930-1931
    - Lay Leader material, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Lay Leader Organization Plans - Report Blanks, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - LLII Programs, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - LLII Rankings and Results, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - LLII Mimeographed Material (Child Guidance), 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - LLII Lay Leader Material Lessons, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Miss Muskal - Extension Rpt's (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Roskelly (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Extension Methods Handbook for the Files of the Training Project Office in the College of Home Economics (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Child Guidance Questionnaires
    - Albany County, 1927-1928 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Buffalo County, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Chautauqua County - Jamestown, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Suffolk County - Riverhead, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Ulster County - Kingston, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 5, Folder 6)
    - St. Lawrence County, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 7, Folder 8)
    - Wayne County, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 9, Folder 10)
    - Ontario County, 1930-1931 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Allegany County, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Herkimer County, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Trip Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Clothing, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Lay Leader Plan and Results, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Study Club Bulletins, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - US Dept. of Agriculture (Prints and Slides), 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Otsego County - Oneonta, Unadilla, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Suffolk County - Riverhead, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Ulster County - Kingston, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Addresses, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Book Lists, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Budget, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Calender, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Conferences, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Expense Accounts - Eastman, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Expense Accounts - Walker, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Study Club Organization Plans & Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Travel Cards - Eastman, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Travel Cards- Walker, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Bibliographies (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Nutrition (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - 1925-1926
    - Monthly Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Trip Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1925-1927 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1926-1927
    - Monthly Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1927-1928
    - Annual Report, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report - Washington, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta Habits, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Blanks - Parent Interviews, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Clothing and Foods, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Farmers Week - Material, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Home Demonstration Agents Conference, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - International Council, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Laura Spellman Rockefeller suggestions, Mrs. Frank, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Material to be Sent - Mrs. Stocking, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Mimeographed Material - Extension, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Minimum Essentials for Nursery School, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Miss Van Rensselear memorandum, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Monthly Report, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - National Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Picture proofs - Home-made toys, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Report on Extension - Dean L. S. Rockerfeller, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Reports from other States - Child Care, Guidance, Etc., 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Reprints, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Resumes -NY State College Courses in Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Stencils send out on request, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Traveling Libraries - NY State, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Trip Reports, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 27)